Trice, Harrison M. Additional Papers /4164
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- An Evaluation of Discipline As a Way to Control Work Performance, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Further Musings from a Cockeyed Optimist, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  Published in Alcoholism: The National Magazine
- Idealized Role Conceptions As Moderators of Perceived Role Overload, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- The Identity Crisis in EAP, prepared for ALMACA 1983 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Introduction - Perspectives on Job-Related Programs for Alcohol and Drug Problems, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Level I EAP Materials, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Level I EAP Materials continued, 1985-1988 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Musings of a Devoted Outsider, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- "The Old Reality" in the Livestock Marketing Congress, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  June 13-15, 1984
- Perspectives on Job-Based Programs for Alcohol and Drug Problems - Part 1, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Research Access, Data Collection and Utilization, 1981-1984 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Role of the Labor Union In Company Based Alcoholism Program, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- University of California, San Diego Conference June 1987 - Strategies for EAP: A Crucial Balance, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  June 4-6, 1987
- Miscellaneous Conferences, 1977-1986 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- Book Review - Implementing Change: Alcoholism Policies in Work Organizations (By C.J. Schramm, G. Zaltman, and J. Muldoon), 1980- 1981 (Box 68, Folder 24)
- Union Involvement in EAP - JH (Box 68, Folder 25)
- Family Systems Theory - Applied (By Thom deLara), 1985 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  Published in EAP Digest
- The Love of Labor, Labor's Love - Mental Health (By B.S. Brown, M.D.), 1969 (Box 68, Folder 27)
- Technological Change and Mental Health (By C. DeCarlo), 1968 (Box 68, Folder 28)
- Staff Advisor's Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Blank Interviewer Form), 1979 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Union Officials Experiences with Alcoholism Programs (Blank Respondent Form), 1979 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Medical Directors' Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Blank Interview Form), 1979 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- General Manager's Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Blank Forms), 1979 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Managerial Experiences with Alcoholism Program (Blank A and B Forms), 1979 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Human Intervention and Motivation Study - Airline Pilots Grant Application, 1977-1979 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Airline Pilots Grant Application continued, 1976-1978 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Airline Pilots Association - Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- HMT Notes and Data - Airline Pilots, 1971-1975 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- United Transportation Union (UTU) EAP Conference, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  April 23-24, 1975
- UTU Conference Memos, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- UTU Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- UTU Press Releases /Press regarding EAP, 1974-1977 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- HMT Notes - History of EAPs, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Memo - Dan Forget, regarding OAC Reports, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Monthly Reporting Forms - Pretest Instruments (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Occupational Alcoholism Consultant Survey Instruments, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- EAP Surveys - Western Electric, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Instrument Appendices, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Alcoholism and Employee Relations - BNA Report and Congressional Record, 1969-1978 (Box 69, Folder 20)
- Central Labor Rehabilitation Council pamphlets, 1972-1976 (Box 69, Folder 21)
- Interview - Gerald Waters, Central Labor Rehabilitation Council, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 22)
- Central Labor Rehabilitation Council of New York - Organizational Overview (Box 69, Folder 23)
- Alcoholism Programs in Unionized Settings - HMT paper (Box 69, Folder 24)
- Evaluating AFL-CIO Alcoholism Counselor Training - Project Grant Application, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 25)
- New York City Central Labor Council Memos, 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Notes - HMT (Box 69, Folder 27)
- New York State Occupational Program Consultants - Graduation Announcement, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 28)
- National Council on Alcoholism - Board Letter, Report, 1973-1980 (Box 69, Folder 29)
- Meeting Minutes - Trice Project, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 30)
- Union Official Codebook and Notes (Box 69, Folder 31)
- Patrick Henry Drug and Alcohol Council - Federal Funding Application, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 32)
- Packard Electric EAP Training Manual (Box 69, Folder 33)
- Alcoholics Anonymous Survey Results, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 34)
- Central Labor Rehabilitation Council of New York, 1973-1977 (Box 69, Folder 35)
- EAP Implementation - Joint Approach (Box 69, Folder 36)
- EAP Consultant Interviews - Trice OAP Consultant Research, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 37)
  October 1986 to March 1987, produced on large, continuous computer printouts
- General EAERP Information - Financial/Student/Faculty, 1986-1989 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- EAERP Recruiting Materials, 1987-1991 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Original EAERP Mailing List (Box 71, Folder 3)
- EAERP Brochures, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Employee Assistance Education and Research Program Rochester Student Roster, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Gary Metz - EAP and Clinical Issues, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Gloria Samson - Labor History, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Gerry Carpenter - Labor History, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Evelyn Hartman - Labor Problems, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Rochester EAERP Dropped Students, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Rochester EAERP Student Files, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Rochester Student Files, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- EAERP Buffalo (Spring 1989) - Funding and Class Roster, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- Buffalo EAERP Miscellaneous Information/Information Request Forms, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Buffalo Student Class Files, 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Class Files - Buffalo, 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Evelyn Hartman-Wakshull - Buffalo, 1987-1989 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Carole F. Bruce and Jackie Elias - Organizational Behavior, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- James Parker - EAP Marketing, 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 19)
- Steven Schwartz - Clinical Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- Buffalo EAERP Final Grades, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- Buffalo Student Information and Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Buffalo - Dropped Students, 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 23)
- EAERP Albany - Student List and Course Information, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  Includes news clippings, includes Social Security Numbers
- Student Registration Form/Grade Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 25)
- Student Registration/Grade Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 26)
- John Quinn - Marketing of EAPs, 1986-1989 (Box 71, Folder 27)
- Albany Dropped Students, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 28)
- Syracuse - Student Records, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 29)
- Syracuse - Student Records, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 30)
- Syracuse EAERP Graduation Program, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 31)
- Syracuse - Labra History Course Outline, 1983-1985 (Box 71, Folder 32)
- Syracuse - Work Organizations Course Outline, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 33)
- Syracuse - Organizational Behavior Course Outline, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 34)
- Syracuse - Student Enrollment, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 35)
- Syracuse - Collective Bargaining Course Materials, 1983-1986 (Box 71, Folder 36)
- Syracuse - Arbitration Course Outline, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 37)
- Syracuse - Interpersonal Behavior Course Outline, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 38)
- Syracuse - Principles of Supervision Course Outline, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 39)
- Syracuse - Student Records, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 40)
- Syracuse - Instructors (Box 71, Folder 41)
- Syracuse - Dropped Students, 1985-1986 (Box 71, Folder 42)
- Directory of EAP Service Providers in New York City, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 43)
- New York City EAERP - Student Files, Winter 1986 (Box 71, Folder 44)
- New York City EAERP - Student Files, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 45)
- Daniel Molloy - New York City EAERP, 1986-1989 (Box 71, Folder 46)
- New York City EAERP - Instructor Correspondence and Syllabus, 1985-1987 (Box 71, Folder 47)
- NYC EAERP Course Roster, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 48)
- Student Applications, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 49)
- NYC Dropped Students, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 50)
- Cornell University and Faculty Federation Bargaining Agreement, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 51)
- Guy Kevin Reed - Case File, 1986-1989 (Box 71, Folder 52)
- Correspondence regarding Gary Dion, 1988-1992 (Box 71, Folder 53)
- Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 71, Folder 54)
- Miscellaneous Notes - HMT, 1963-1986 (Box 71, Folder 55)
- Field Diary - Alcoholics Anonymous - Richard Sirota and HMT (Box 71, Folder 56)
- Smithers Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Published Information regarding Smithers (Annual Reports and Public Relations items), 1977-1985 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Smithers Budget Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Smithers Financial Information April 1987-July 1989, 1986-1989 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Smithers - Income/Expense Allocation Forms (April 1988-February 1990), 1988-1990 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Courses Taught by Trice 1966-1981 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous ILR Correspondence, 1966-1987 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- ILR Student Paper (Weiss, Richard) (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Student Work, 1968-1986 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- ILR Graduate Student Association, 1976-1982 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- EAERP Funding, 1987-1990 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Program on Alcoholism and Occupational Health (PAOH) Proposal for Level I Seminars 1989 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Albany EAP Courses, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Buffalo EAP Courses, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- New York City EAP Courses and Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Rochester EAP Courses, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- EAP - Rutgers University Courses, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 17)
- Syracuse EAP Courses Fall 1983 till Spring 1986, 1983-1986 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Syracuse EAP Courses - April 1986-May1986 and unsorted, 1986-1989 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous EAP Courses and Correspondence, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous EAP Courses, 1983-1986 (Box 72, Folder 21)
- EAERP Alumni Conference #1, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 22)
- EAERP Alumni Council #2, 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 23)
- ALMACA Printed Literature (PR), 1983 (Box 72, Folder 24)
- ALMACA Conferences (1979, 1985) (Box 72, Folder 25)
- ALMACA (Georgia), 10th Southeastern EAP Institute, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  April 28-May 3, 1985, includes a street map of the vicinity of the Peachtree Plaza Hotel in Atlanta
- ALMACA Miscellaneous Documents, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  Includes an ALMACA Certificate of Membership for the Cornell School of Industrial and Labor Relations
- Eagleville Hospital Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 72, Folder 28)
- NCA (National Council on Alcoholism) Constitution, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 29)
- NCA Board Letter (January 1977-November 1979), 1977-1979 (Box 72, Folder 30)
- NCA - Membership Plan, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 31)
- NCA Correspondence, 1965-1980 (Box 72, Folder 32)
- NCA 1980 Delegates Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 72, Folder 33)
- NCA Reports, Minutes, and Miscellaneous Documents, 1978-1980 (Box 72, Folder 34)
- NCAAP (NCA) Correspondence and Minutes (July 1979-January 11,1980), 1979-1980 (Box 72, Folder 35)
- NCAAP (NCA) January 11, 1980-March 4,1980, 1979-1980 (Box 72, Folder 36)
- 37A- A Harrison Trice Papers. Large spread sheets (Box 73)
- 55A - Research data on various companies (Box 74)